Welcome to ARC, the Advising and
Registration Companion AI Powered Agent.
ARC was designed to help University of
South Carolina students obtain answers to
frequently asked questions about
advising and registration processes,
procedures, and requirements.
Let’s dive in!
ARC is designed to provide
information specific to the end user.
The first step is to guide the user
through selecting their program.
Users can search for their major
or use the dropdown features.
For those undecided, we have
an option for general guidance.
Once a major is selected, the tool
confirms it is focused on the content for
that major.
Notice the switch major option
in the top right corner.
The ability to switch majors is available
to the end user at all times to allow
users to potentially
compare different majors.
At this point, users can ask predefined
questions that are listed to help them
get started, or they can
ask their own questions.
It is important to note that data is
input and reviewed by subject matter
experts from three levels
of the organization:
university wide administrative content,
college specific content, and major
specific content.
ARC intelligently analyzes all levels
of content associated with the major and
returns an answer which also includes
confidence levels, sources referenced, and
important notes.
All data must have an owner, appropriate
scope tags, effective terms, and Source
URLs.
Let’s get into a couple examples:
In this example we have selected
the Bachelor of Music major and are
highlighting a question about
progression requirements.
ARC searched the source content and
returned a response that is found in the
major level content.
In our next example, the user asks about
a deadline for dropping a class without
a W.
ARC appropriately returned the policy
details found in the university wide
administrative data level.
In the final examples, the user asks
a question that highlights the safety
boundaries designed in ARC.
The user asks what
elective is the easiest.
ARC will refuse questions unrelated to
its purpose and will return a generic
response redirecting the user.
If the user were to ask a question
concerning information not in the source
data, ARC will not provide responses
for questions that it does not have
adequate source information and points
to relevant contact information for the
advising team.
Thank you for learning more about ARC!